[Music]
hello everyone and my name is p bashal
welcome back to my channel as I promise
I will create a video about FWD
funds for today's
video FWD
funds quarterly payout let's get started
what are this funds so it's actually the
FWD peso Nitro Global payout fund and
FWD peso velocity it will give you a non
guaranteed Target payout for unit per
year sa peso Nitro 5,800 per 100,000
units and sa peso velocity Nam 2,800 per
100,000 unit peso Nitro is an aggressive
fund and peso velocity is
moderate risk profile if you're
conservative moderate or aggressive risk
taker prev
video and description box if you want
more Equity exposure choose Nitro and if
you want to be invested in bond choose
velocity now how do they work
by the way this
F is only available in FWD allet hire
allet hire is a one time or single pay
V now how do they
work declaration date the date when the
payout amount per unit for each
investment fund will be declared then
payout date so after the Declaration
date 20 working days receive payout
frequency of payout is quarterly and
take note it's non guaranteed okay non
guaranteed Target payout per unit per
case here in FWD I will show you
later cents and the product is all set
higher let me just explain further the
non guaranteed Target payout per unit an
the payout may change due to unforeseen
or extraordinary events that will change
the ability of the fund to provide a
payout the natural volatility of the
market or even a recession does not
change the fund's ability to make a pay
P out for example covid-19 would not
have stopped the payout even though it
was a major disruption in the economy it
still did not change the investment
environment enough to necessitate a
changeid 19 just added to Market
volatility
meaning Market volatility that
means is net asset value per unit so the
target amount may change every quarter
due to the foreign exchange component if
the US dollar is strong expect the
payout to be higher if the US dollar is
weak expect the payout to be lower while
FWD has the legal rights to change the
target payout amount we are highly
incentivized to maintain it since it is
the nature of the fund it will take an
extraordinary event before the
payout number
ofs times the target payout per
unit Target payout per unit on the
Declaration
date pay per un every payout
automatic bank account at the same time
your fund enjoys exposure to a
diversified Global
portfolio let me give you an example
Lopez 40-year-old female allet higher
minimum allet higher is 1 million so CLA
single pay 2 million pesos one time pay
all set higher then f is FWD Nitro fund
aggressive assuming
PES invest 2 million pesos 2 million 1
PES that means un CL total of 2 million
units 2 million divided one inest FWD
Nitro that means aggressive risk taker C
CLA automatically 2.5 million life
insurance or death benefit if something
happens
to even though
mil atically if pass
away cost of
insurance
P that's 150 PES per month cost of
insurance the F value or units okay so
hold
on million units minus 150
units COI every month charges if
something happens to her
2.5 or C of insurance or outstanding
units is
1,999 850 formula again is number of
units times the target payout per unit
November 10th 2022 for example declare
company Target payout per unit is 014 5
per quarter so number of units Claire
times the target payout per unit so
1,999 850 units times
0.0145 that means December 12 2023
receive 28,0
9978 pesos as her quarterly
payout allet and Nitro fund and then
December 12 assuming 4% fund fund value
is now 2,
6,381
pesos
28,000 next declaration date February 10
declare Target payout per unit February
10 2023
0145 per quarter for
example every month is 150 un for the
COI is
1,999 550 units minus another 50 units
for the COI for that month and then
units is
1,999 400 that means times
0.145 Target payout per unit payout is
on March 10 and the amount is
28,990 pesos and then assuming UL
assuming the word is assuming 4% fund
now her fund value is
p May 10 declaration date number of
units n is
1,998 and 950 units time
0.0145 olet so June 7 Mar receive
28,9
18478 as her third payout third quarter
and assuming 4% June 7 so F value will
now become 2 million
4,223 pesos May pay out L PA F value no
assuming at 4
what 4% 6% 8% 10% and DEP again
investment
guarante will depend on the actual fund
performance next is August 10
declaration another payout which
is is
1,998 500 units times the target payout
per unit the same P
0145 so payout amount reive on September
7th is
28978 25 pesos and 4% F will now become
2, 64,9 45 pesos if we will total payout
reive
cled is 11 15,9 5215 pesos plus the
current account value or fund value
assuming at 4% growth 2,782
[Music]
pesos now let me share with you the
actual performance peso Nitro Global
payout fund website
fwd.com and F and aggressive fund Nitro
Global payout
fund date today is July 29 today while
and filming is July 29 2024 and unit
price is 1.06 736 that means Tas na
talaga to is 1 PES now it's 1.06 na per
unit and a y screen if you will draw a
straight line there's no way but to go
up it's fluctuating
per and this is the fund's return 1
month ago
1.67% if you invested 3 months ago
4.20% if you invested one year ago wow
kumita 13.69%
oh my God 1 million is
1.13
130,000 G Inception 8.79% annual xita
where the funds are invested an asset
allocation chart region and payout
hisory declaration dates left side
November 2022 2023 oh every quarter
receive pay cents and a payout amount
per unit I I4 729
03830 and then recent May 10
2024 cents
04574 per unit nil payout and annualized
rate and this time K PES velocity Global
payout fund f is
1.1 per unima Lang sa piso Ayan if you
will also see the graph ay Ka screen
historical fun performance chart
noal one year ago invest velocity 133%
13.74%
and since Inception
8.83 and aay
hisory
invel and that's all for this video I
hope this
time Fay which is Nitro and
velocity if you want to start investing
and you want to receive a quarterly
payout at the same time
insured
invest and let me ass
priority let's sit down and let me help
you plan financially for your future
again about the risk profile and about
allet H thank you so much for watching
if this video helped you don't forget to
like comment subscribe YouTube channel
and follow me Tik Tok Peach abash
question just comment down below and if
ready to take charge for your future
message and let me help you plan
financially for your future and let your
money work for you this time always
remember your life is a gift from God
what you do with it is your gift to God
thank you so much and God bless everyone
bye
[Music]